How is that person?
It's a guy....he was instinctively looking for his son and got lost here
He said let him stay here
Looking for son?
Mr.Sam!!
How are your friends?
Yeah ,they're fine
You don't have to worry for them
I have....
I know
That girl's ability to change gender is a forbidden ability
It is not allowed to exist in any era or on anyone
Are you want to....?
Find and bring that girl to me
But what about what we did plan...
BRING THAT GTRL HERE NOW
What the....
Do you know where Hoan is?
Are you two real girls?
No we are not
We were played around by that ghost girl
Oh..
Do you know where she is?
From what I see, that girl often flies around this town to scare people
Usually appears at night
Why is the exit from his residence the location of the Spring Gem?
( Blocked by the wirls of color in the night, only one color can pass through like a moving flower )
Maybe I can't get any more information from him
I have to use the last method
Oai!!?
Bro, It's me
STOP !! IT'S ME KE!!!
Look up
Why are you up....
You can use that ability on yourself?
I was counterattacked
Can't you turn back yourself?
No...
Because no one has ever countered this ability of mine before
So who?
A woman and she is not a human
She has horns and aqua eyes without pupils
Plus she has a very sexy body
But why are you sitting here?
If I wasn't sitting here, you wouldn't be able to talk to me like this
Why you say sound scary?
Now I need you to stay away from that entity person
And I don't need you to spy around anymore and stop messing around that town
I will deal with it myself
What about my shape?
That's the result of not listening to me
Try to get used to it for a while
You're such a bad cousin